ต่อไปฉันจะโชว์คุณว่า
วิธีการปรับใช้ uniswap กับ Acala
บล็อคเชน
ฉันอยากจะลองใช้เหรียญ ripple
ตรงๆดูแต่น่าเสียดายว่า uniswap
ใช้เหรียญ ripple เวอร์ชันเก่ามาก
ดังนั้น มันจะยุ่งยากที่จะย้าย
ไปเป็น
เวอร์ชันใหม่เพื่อให้เข้ากับทั้งสอง
ดังนั้นฉัน
จึงนำ artifact มาจาก uniswap
ripple
นี่คือไฟล์ json
ความจริงแล้วให้ฉัน เอ่อ
ให้ฉัน
deploy(แปลง) สัญญา
ให้ testnet ของเรา
และนี่คือ setup ที่ระบบต้องการ
ใน deploy  ใน deploy.js
คุณจะเห็น
โค้ด ซึ่งจะค่อนข้างธรรมดา
ตรงไปตรงมา ไม่มีอะไรพิเศษ
สำหรับ acala จะเห็นได้ว่ามันเป็นแค่โปรเจ็ค
ธรรมดา คุณจะเห็น
ตรงนี้ ฉันได้สร้าง Aca Token
contract สำหรับ
โทเค็น acala และ dot อันนี้คือ
address ของบัญชี
และนี่คือระบบของสัญญาดังนั้นเราสามารถ
คุณสามารถเลือก address
คุณจะเห็นได้ว่าเรา
ตั้งมันให้เรียบง่าย
จากนั้นเราจะ deploy UniswapFactory
contract และก็ deploy UniswapRouter
contract
โดยแค่ใส่ไปใน address
approve เราสามารถ
ทำการโยกย้าย หรือเพิ่มสภาพคล่อง
หรือสามารถปริ๊นข้อมูลต่างๆได้
นี่คือสิ่งสคริปต์พื้นฐานของทำงานของ
deploy
บนเทสเน็ตของเรา คุณสามารถเห็น
การ deploy เราเตอร์ไปที่ address นี้
ฉันไปเปลี่ยน address ตรงนี้
และรันสคริปต์โดยสคริปต์นี้
นำยูนิตของ router ไป
พิสูจน์
uh check some balance and do a unit
slope trade
that's in this case you try to sell some
of those to buy some sale token
um so it would try to sell exactly one
dot to buy
hong kong to buy a sound amount of sa
and this will print the balance to
verify if the trade is success
so it's running on this net so you can
see um the before
balance the trade after balance so the
dos amount reduced by one
the ac amount increased by roughly one
yep you can check the liquidity
pool in the trading period
you can see um this one charges some
amount of liquidity fee as well
so this is basically um how you can
like write a scrap to trade unit
with the scrap so obviously you can't
easily connect this to your existing
ui to get things working
um in the setup js we don't do too much
in special special things so
what we do especially basically create a
provider so this
case in this case this is uh ether's
provider so it's offered the implemented
by the body
implementing the provider interface
abstract provider interface of esos
so it's abstract provider so it works
with css
js and this takes a websocket provider
which is basically in a node url
wait for community create the
creator signing keep here so you will be
using the one coming from the
environment variable which i have
defined
myself or it just takes the test
keep here if you're running this on your
local test name
and create a signing key create a signer
and this is the again
abstract signus from the ethers
yes and that's pretty much it so now you
with this will
then you can just use it as a normal
um wallet
and this should just work with your
existing deployment scrapper and other
scrap they're using ethers js so this is
basically
um how you can deploy
the unit swap contracts into our test
net
and or if you want you can also deploy
this to your local network so
you just if you don't set up any
environment